

# **RAFAEL MORALES**

Digital Marketer International MBA in Digital Marketing

## PERSONAL HISTORY

Professional with 7 years of work experience, over 3 years of experience in the IT industry and 3 years working in digital marketing. Experience working in eCommerce projects, design and execution of SEO strategy, website development, marketing campaign management and inbound strategies.

## SKILLS AND ABILITIES

- SEO & SEM
- · Inbound Marketing
- · Analytics & Monitoring
- Remarketing

# PLATFORMS AND TOOLS

- Google (Analytics + Ads + Tag Manager)
- Google (Merchant Center + Console)
- WordPress + WooCommerce
- Facebook Ads / Store + Wapp Business

# **CONTACT INFO**

WhatsApp: <u>+57 3052661440</u> rafaelmorales112@hotmail.com Current Location: Bogotá, Colombia

My Portfolio

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **SEO Manager (Freelance)**

Active Visions Group | 02/2020 - Present

- Creation of online stores and SEO strategy of the brands.
- Organic traffic growth from 0 to 4000 monthly visits.

# **Digital Marketing Manager (Freelance)**

Iluminar Ltda. | 11/2018 - Present

- Increased repeat buying from 10% to 35%.
- · Achieved a 300% ROI in marketing campaigns.
- Organic traffic growth from 0 to 5000 monthly visitors.

## **SEO Specialist**

Zeus Tecnología | 10/2017 - 10/2018

- Organic traffic growth from 4K to 10K monthly visitors.
- Creation and execution of inbound and social media strategy.

#### **BI Consultant**

#### **Zeus Tecnología** | 06/2015 - 10/2017

- Development of the financial panel to end-user increased the license acquisition of BI department by 25%.
- Managed a team of developers for the IFRS financial statement automation project launching and implementation.

## **EDUCATION**

#### M.Sc. International MBA

ESIC Business & Marketing School - SISU | 2018 - 2020

#### M.sc. Tax Managemet

Universidad Tecnológica | 2017 - 2018

#### **B.Sc. Business Administrator**

Universidad del Norte | 2009 - 2014